learneredge.com 2018-08-27

# 

SpryMediaOnline, a California corporation (hereafter “SpryMediaOnline”) is dedicated to establishing a trusting relationships with its registered users, based on respect for personal identity and information, by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy policy (“Policy”) covers the www.SpryMediaOnline.com website (hereafter the “Site). Because SpryMediaOnline wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users' privacy, we are disclosing:

  1. What personally identifiable information SpryMediaOnline collects.   

  2. How SpryMediaOnline uses the information.   

  3. With whom SpryMediaOnline may share user information.   

  4. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.   

  5. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under SpryMediaOnline control.   

  6. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.   

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact SpryMediaOnline Customer Support by email using the "Contact Us" page.

**Information Collection and Use**

**Information Collection**  
SpryMediaOnline is the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. SpryMediaOnline collects information from its users at several different points on our Site.

**Registration**  
In order to use SpryMediaOnline services which are a pre-pay service, a user must first complete the registration process. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name, email address, telephone number, home address, etc), a unique identifier, and financial information (such as credit card information, billing address, etc.). We use this information to contact the user about services on our Site for which the user has expressed interest and to provide those services and bill user for the services. 

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user's personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Site, and to potentially direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share personally identifiable elements of your profile with other third parties. Your profile is shared in aggregate form only.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.   
By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user might be limited in some areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the "Profile" section, above. 

**Log Files**  
Like most Web sites, our servers use log files to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Clear Gifs**  
Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information.  
We may also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section.

**Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new registered users a welcoming email to verify a new user’s contact information and PIN or password. Existing registered users will occasionally receive emails containing information about us, service related announcements, information about third party services that are likely to be of interest to our members, and member satisfaction questions. 

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and regarding issues relating to their accounts. We reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Sharing**

          Marketing Partners  
We may from time to time share your personal information with third party marketing partners who may send you offers for goods and services which you may find of interest.

          Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or where we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding or administrative hearing, or other legal process served on our Site. For example, SpryMediaOnline may disclose personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or third parties in response to criminal or civil subpoenas. If we do receive a request to disclose a registered user’s personal information, we will notify user of such request at the email or telephone number recorded in our database at that time. Users are advised to keep current their contact information on file with us and update it accordingly.

          Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

          Third Party Intermediaries  
We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies have contracted with us not to retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

          Business Transitions  
In the event SpryMediaOnline goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given a choice not to have their information used in this different manner, as described in the notification of changes section, below.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
If at any time you decide you no longer wish to receive communications from us or third parties you can unsubscribe here:  http://learneredge.com/unsubscribe.aspx. Please note that third parties with whom we have already shared your information will not receive this request and you may unsubscribe from those sites using the mechanism in the emails they send. 

**Links**  
This Site may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that SpryMediaOnline is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Statement applies solely to information collected by this Site. SpryMediaOnline may enter into advertising and affiliate relationships with third party web sites which drive interested parties to our Site. Information that is collected on these third party sites are not controlled by this Policy, and users are advised to read the separate privacy policies of these web sites. 

**Surveys**  
Periodically, our Site might request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of SpryMediaOnline's services. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and a choice to opt-out. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys, they may not use customers' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Security**  
SpryMediaOnline takes precaution to protect its users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the SpryMediaOnline's Web Site, their information is protected both online and off-line.  
When our registration/order forms ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number, billing information, etc.), that information is encrypted and is protected using industry standard encryption software (128 bit secure socket layers protocols).   
While we use SSL encryption protocols to protect sensitive information online, we also employ security measures to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerks or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment.

**Supplementation of Information**   
In order for SpryMediaOnline to properly fulfill its obligations to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. SpryMediaOnline may verify the billing address on all credit card transactions and may obtain credit reports for some customers. The information obtained from these third party sources is maintained in a manner consistent with SpryMediaOnline's privacy Policy.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. Users may login in to their account and then access the profile page to change any personal information, or they may contact us by email using the "Contact Us" page. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Policy, we will post those changes in this Policy, and other places we deem appropriate, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the Site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding this Policy, please contact us through the "Contact Us" page or by clicking this link: [ http://learneredge.com/contact_us.aspx](http://learneredge.com/contact_us.aspx).
